

949.381.9867 rolandolopantzi.com rlopantzi@gmail.com

Right away it doesn't seem like much, this will most likely be overlooked because of the lack of experience that I have for the field and I totally get it. What you don't know is that I'm willing to put in the work to learn and grow. If I run into a problem, I will do my best to try to solve it on my own before asking someone for help. For the past couple of years Google and YouTube have been my best friends in learning new skills and for finding solutions or clues to my problems that I run into. Positivity plays a big role in my life, I'm always moving forward and with a 100% attitude. I know the knowledge isn't there, **yet**, but if you're interested in finding out more about me and would be willing to give me 2-5 minutes of your time to chat, I'd be more than honored.

Qualifications

HTML & CSS	
JavaScript	
Illustrator	
Photshop & Indesign	

Education

Team Treehouse, Udemy and Free Code Camp Front End Development

Winter 2017 - Present

Orange Coast College *GED*

Fall 2011 - Spring 2012

Newport Harbor High School *Diploma* 2006 - 2010

Work History

Expert Coating & Graphics, Anaheim, Ca

Logistics Coordinator & Designer

- Check to see if raw material is good to process
- Prepare good raw material to get processed
- Inventory control of all raw material that we have for each customer
- Oversee that artwork gets printed correctly, matching colors and dimensions

Techna-Print, Placentia, Ca

Graphic Designer

- Provide proofs (mock ups) of products with various artwork that client needs
- Redraw artwork or logos if client does not have vector artwork
- Provide good communication skills both in English and Spanish
- Multitask working with phone and computer even with multiple clients
- Make sure that artwork gets printed out correctly for Screen or Plate printing

State Farm Insurance Company, Fullerton, Ca

Translator, Customer Service

- Provide good communication skills both in English and in Spanish
- Multitask working with phone and computer even with multiple clients
- Taking payments mostly, credit card payments
- Scheduling appointments with clients

Internship & Volunteer Experience

- The Design Office (4 months) Designing logo's, business cards & brochures
- Airfind (1 month) Mobile application design, UI design
- Catechism group leader at St. Joachim Church (2 yrs)
- Librarian assistant at Mariners Public Library (1 yr)

Sept 2018 - Present

May 2015 - Aug 2018

Aug 2014 - May 2015